http://www.attraction-tickets-direct.co.uk/en/privacy-policy.htm

Log in
My basket (#)
Disney's 7 Day Ultimate Ticket
Disney After Hours - Unique Nighttime Experiences at Walt Disney World
ICON Orlando™ Champagne Experience
Icon Park Big Three Combo: The Wheel, Madame Tussauds & Sealife Aquarium
SEA LIFE Orlando
SEA LIFE Orlando
SEA LIFE Orlando Admission Ticket
Madame Tussauds Orlando & SEA LIFE Combo Ticket
Icon Park Big Three Combo: The Wheel, Madame Tussauds & Sealife Aquarium
Madame Tussauds Orlando
Madame Tussauds Orlando
Madame Tussauds Orlando Admission Ticket
Madame Tussauds Orlando & SEA LIFE Combo Ticket
Icon Park Big Three Combo: The Wheel, Madame Tussauds & Sealife Aquarium
Sleuths Mystery Dinner Show
WonderWorks & the Outta Control Magic Comedy Dinner VIP Combo Ticket
Go Miami Explorer Pass
Florida Everglades Airboat Rides at Sawgrass Recreation Park
Florida Everglades Airboat Rides at Sawgrass Recreation Park
Best Value New York Combo Tickets
Empire State Building & Statue of Liberty Cruise Combo Saver
Madame Tussauds New York Tickets
MoMA – The Museum of Modern Art with Skip-the-Line Admission
Big Bus New York Hop-On Hop-Off Bus Tour
All Around Town Tour Hop-on Hop-Off Bus Tour with Harbour Cruise
Spirit New York Dinner Cruise
Bateaux New York Bottomless Mimosa Sunday Buffet Brunch Cruise
Essential Statue Tour
Exclusive Disney on Broadway Tour: Behind the Magic at the New Amsterdam Theatre
Guided 9/11 Memorial Tour with Museum Tickets
Meet The Met: Extended Metropolitan Museum of Art Tour
Stories from the Dark Side of New York: Criminals, Gangs & Mafia Crime Tour
One World Observatory & World Trade Centre Tour
Tenements, Tastings, and Tales – A Small Group Tour of NY’s Lower East Side
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island Fully Escorted Tour PLUS Pedestal Access
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island Fully Escorted Tour
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island RESERVE Ticket
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island RESERVE Ticket PLUS Pedestal Access
Statue of Liberty, Ellis Island And 9/11 Memorial & Museum Tour
Early Access Statue of Liberty Tour with Ellis Island
Statue of Liberty, Ellis Island And 9/11 Memorial & Museum Tour
Essential Statue Tour
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island Fully Escorted Tour
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island RESERVE Ticket PLUS Pedestal Access
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island RESERVE Ticket
Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island Fully Escorted Tour PLUS Pedestal Access
Meet The Met: Extended Metropolitan Museum of Art Tour
Met Express: Highlights of the Metropolitan Museum of Art in 2 Hours
MoMA – The Museum of Modern Art with Skip-the-Line Admission
Universal Studios Hollywood Tickets
Disneyland California and Universal Studios Hollywood Combo Ticket
Universal Studios Hollywood Buy a Day Get a 2nd Day Free Special Offer Ticket
Disneyland California
Disneyland California 2 Day Ticket (One Park Per Day)
Disneyland California 3 Day Ticket (One Park Per Day)
Disneyland California 3-Day Hopper Ticket
Disneyland California 4 Day Ticket (One Park Per Day)
Disneyland California 4-Day Hopper Ticket
Disneyland California 5 Day Ticket (One Park Per Day)
Disneyland California 5-Day Hopper Ticket
Disneyland California 2-Day Hopper Ticket
Disneyland California and Universal Studios Hollywood Combo Ticket
Disneyland California
Hollywood Celebrity Homes Tour & Warner Bros. Studio Tour from Anaheim
Paris Montparnasse Observation Deck Tickets
Louvre Museum Independent Audio Tour with Skip the Line Access
Louvre Museum Guided Tour with Skip the Line Access
Closing Time At The Louvre: The Mona Lisa At Her Most Peaceful
Louvre Highlights Small Group Tour: Mona Lisa, Venus de Milo & Winged Victory
Skip-the-line Eiffel Tower Ticket
Sightseeing Tours and Tickets
Sightseeing Tours and Tickets
Paris Seinorama - Skip the Line Eiffel Tower Visit, Paris City Tour and Seine Cruise
Big Bus Paris Hop-on Hop-off Bus Tour
Eiffel Tower Dinner, Seine River Cruise and the Moulin Rouge
Heart of Paris: Île de la Cité, Seine Cruise, River Walking Tour, and Skip-the-Line Sainte Chapelle
Paris Sightseeing Cruise
Paris Bike Tour
Paris in a Day Small Group Tour with Skip the Line Louvre Museum, Eiffel Tower, Montmartre & Seine River Cruise
Small Group Tour to Bath and Stonehenge from London
Small Group Tour to Oxford, Stratford and Cotswolds with 2-Course Lunch from London
Small Group Tour to Oxford, Stratford and Cotswolds with 2-Course Lunch from London
Small Group Tour to Windsor Castle and Stonehenge from London
Small Group Tour to Windsor, Bath and Stonehenge from London
Small Group Tour to Windsor, Bath and Stonehenge from London
The lastminute.com London Eye
Warner Bros. Studio Tour London - The Making of Harry Potter with Return Transportation
Warner Bros. Studio Tour London - The Making of Harry Potter with Return Transportation
Warner Bros. Studio Tour London - The Making of Harry Potter with Return Transportation from Kings Cross
Warner Bros. Studio Tour + 4-hour Hop-On Hop-Off London Bus Tour
Warner Bros. Studio Tour London - The Making of Harry Potter with Return Transportation from Victoria
Sightseeing Cruises
Sightseeing Cruises
Bateaux London River Thames Lunch Cruise
The Ultimate London Speedboat Experience
The View from The Shard and Thames Sightseeing Cruise for Two - Experience Voucher
Bateaux London River Thames Dinner Cruise
Sunday Lunch River Thames Jazz Cruise
River Thames Sightseeing Cruise - River Red Rover Hopper Ticket
Sightseeing Tickets
Panoramic Tour of London with St Paul's Cathedral and Guard Change
West End Shows - The Lion King
West End Shows - Mamma Mia!
Experiences & Gifts
The Dare Skywalk at Tottenham Hotspur Stadium Experience Voucher
Outer Barrier Reef Adventure from Cairns
Silversonic Outer Barrier Reef Snorkelling and Diving Adventure from Cairns
Silverswift Outer Barrier Reef Snorkelling and Diving Adventure
Daintree Walkabout from Port Douglas
Flames of the Forest Rainforest Dining Experience from Port Douglas
Great Barrier Reef Scenic Helicopter Flight from Port Douglas
Kuranda, Skyrail & Scenic Rail from Port Douglas
Outer Barrier Reef Adventure from Port Douglas
Silversonic Outer Barrier Reef Snorkelling and Diving Adventure from Port Douglas
Reykjavik
Airport Transfer and Blue Lagoon Admission - Comfort Experience
Blue Lagoon Admission
Blue Lagoon Admission
Airport Transfer and Blue Lagoon Admission - Comfort Experience
Airport Transfer and Blue Lagoon Admission - Premium Experience
Reykjavik Express Airport Transfers
Keflavik Airport to Reykjavik Hotels Airport Arrival Transfer
Keflavik Airport to Reykjavik Hotels Return Airport Transfer
Golden Circle Classic and Fontana Geothermal Baths
The Golden Circle Classic - Gullfoss, Geysir and Thingvellir
Vatican Museums Night Tour with Sistine Chapel
The Complete Vatican Tour With Vatican Museums, Sistine Chapel & St. Peter's Basilica
Pristine Sistine Early Entrance Small Group Vatican Tour
Skip the line Vatican Museums & St. Peter's Basilica Tour
Rome Hop-on/Hop-off Bus Tour plus Skip-the-Line Vatican Museums Entry
Rome Hop-on/Hop-off Bus Tour Plus SKIP THE LINE Colosseum, Vatican Museums and Sistine Chapel Entry
VIP Pristine Sistine Vatican Tour with Museum Breakfast
Papal Audience at Vatican City
Colosseum Tickets
Colosseum Tickets
Rome Hop-on/Hop-off Double Decker Bus Tour plus Skip-the-Line Colosseum Entry
Imperial Rome Elite Walking Tour with Skip-the-Line Colosseum Ticket
VIP Caesar's Palace Tour with Colosseum and Roman Forum
Rome Hop-on/Hop-off Bus Tour Plus SKIP THE LINE Colosseum, Vatican Museums and Sistine Chapel Entry
Rome Sightseeing
Biking, Walking & Segway Tours
Biking, Walking & Segway Tours
Early Entry Sistine Chapel & St Peter's Basilica Express Service
St. Peter’s Basilica from Top to Bottom with Dome Climb & Crypt
Guided Visit to the Accademia Gallery and Uffizi
All Florence in One Day including the Academy and Uffizi Galleries.
Best of Florence Audiopen Self-Guided Walking Tour
Dine Around Florence: An Authentic Evening Food and Wine Experience
Florence Hop-on Hop-off Double Decker Bus Tour
Florence Hop-on Hop-off Double Decker Bus Tour
Florence Hop-On Hop-Off Bus Tour with Accademia Gallery Guided Tour
Florence Hop-On Hop-Off Bus Tour with Skip-the-line Guided Tour of Duomo Cathedral
Florence Hop-On Hop-Off Bus Tour with Uffizi Gallery Guided Tour
Florence Hop-on Hop-off Double Decker Bus Tour
Florence Medici's Mile - Walking along the Path of Medici Residence and Vasari Corridor
Florence “Duomo Monumental Complex” Guided Tour
Guided Visit to the Accademia Gallery with Skip-the-Line Admission
Learn to make Pizza & Gelato
Skip the Line Florence Duomo Brunelleschi's Dome Tour
Small Group: Florence In a Day with David, Duomo, Uffizi, and Walking Tour
Uffizi Gallery
Uffizi Gallery
Guided Visit to the Uffizi Gallery with Skip-the-Line Admission
Exclusive Alone In St. Mark's And Doge's Palace Tour
Original Venice Walking Tour with Skip-the-line Entrance to St Mark’s Basilica
Original Venice Walking Tour with Skip-the-line Entrance to St Mark’s Basilica
Gondola Ride & Original Venice Walking Tour
Original Venice Walking Tour with Skip-the-line Entrance to St Mark’s Basilica
Skip The Line Doge's Palace Tour
Small Group Grand Canal Boat Tour
Small Group: Venice Boat Tour with Grand Canal & Tower Climb
VIP Alone in St. Mark’s Basilica After Hours
VIP Alone in St. Mark’s Basilica After Hours
Exclusive Alone In St. Mark's And Doge's Palace Tour
VIP Alone in St. Mark’s Basilica After Hours
Venice Food Tour: Rialto Market, Cannaregio, Gondola, Food & Wine
Venice Hop-on/Hop-off Canal Cruise
Venice Super Saver Tour: Doge's Palace, Venice Walking Tour with St Mark’s Basilica & Grand Canal Cruise
Atlantis Aquaventure Waterpark
Atlantis Aquaventure One Day Super Pass with Free Lost Chambers Aquarium
Aquaventure Water Park Day Pass
Atlantis Sea Lion Discovery Programme
Dolphin Bay at Atlantis The Palm
Dolphin Bay at Atlantis The Palm
Atlantis Dolphin Adventure Deep Water Interaction at Dolphin Bay
Dubai Parks and Resorts 1 Day/2 Park Ticket
Dubai Parks And Resorts 1 Day All Parks Ticket with Q-Fast Pass
Burj Khalifa Observation Deck Tickets
At the Top of the World - Burj Khalifa & lunch at Burj Al Arab
Ski Dubai
Dubai Sightseeing
Dubai Sightseeing
Big Bus Dubai Hop-on Hop-off Tour
Dubai City Sightseeing Hop-On Hop-Off Double Decker Bus Tour
90-minute Speedboat Tour: Marina, Atlantis, Palm & Burj Al Arab
Dubai Marina Luxury Yacht Share Cruise
Dubai Marina Luxury Yacht Share Morning Cruise with Breakfast
Dubai Marina Luxury Yacht Share Afternoon Cruise with BBQ
Dubai Marina Luxury Yacht Share Sunset Cruise with BBQ
90-minute Speedboat Tour: Marina, Atlantis, Palm & Burj Al Arab
Evening Dhow Dinner Cruise on Dubai Creek
Dubai Hot Air Balloon Flight with Vintage Land Rover Drive & Desert Breakfast
3 Day PortAventura & Ferrari Land Ticket
3 Day PortAventura, Ferrari Land & Caribe Aquatic Park Ticket
4 Day PortAventura, Ferrari Land & Caribe Aquatic Park Ticket
7 Day PortAventura, Ferrari Land & Caribe Aquatic Park Ticket
Amsterdam Hop On Hop Off Bus Tour Ticket
Amsterdam Hop On Hop Off Bus Tour with Amsterdam Icebar Admission
Amsterdam Hop On Hop Off Bus Tour with Fast Track Rijksmuseum Admission
Candlelight Cruise Including Wine and Cheese
Dutch Masters and Marvels - Luxury Small Group Tour Van Gogh Museum and Rijksmuseum
Auckland Whale & Dolphin Safari
Bay of Islands Day Tour with Hole in the Rock Dolphin Cruise from Auckland
Auschwitz-Birkenau Memorial and Museum Tour
Bestseller Package: Auschwitz-Birkenau and Wieliczka Salt Mine Tour
Golden Eagle Helicopter Tour of the Grand Canyon
Grand Canyon West Rim Helicopter & Skip the Line Skywalk Tour
Grand Canyon Helicopter & Zipline Adventure Tour
Grand Canyon Celebration Helicopter Tour & Black Canyon Rafting
River Adventure - Departing from Grand Canyon National Park
Canyon Spirit Deluxe Helicopter Tour - Departing from Grand Canyon South Rim
North Canyon Tour - Departing from Grand Canyon National Park
The Desert View of the Grand Canyon
The Desert View Sunset Tour of the Grand Canyon
The Hermit's Rest Tour of the Grand Canyon
The Grand Entrance Sunset Tour of the Grand Canyon
The Grand Entrance Jeep Tour of the Grand Canyon - Departing from Grand Canyon National Park
Grand Canyon South Rim Coach Tour with Helicopter
Grand Canyon West Rim Coach Tour with Helicopter and Boat Cruise
Madame Tussauds Las Vegas Tickets
Madame Tussauds Las Vegas and the High Roller Bar Experience
North Beach Pub Tour
San Francisco Self-Guided Bike Tour (24-Hour Rental)
Day Trip to Monterey and Carmel
California Wine Country - Full Day Tour to Sonoma and Napa from San Francisco
California Wine Country - Half Day Tour to Sonoma from San Francisco
Seattle
Boeing Factory Tour including Future of Flight Aviation Center
Free COVID Cancellation Cover
Full ticket refund within 21 Days if your holiday is disrupted by attraction or border closures or the FCO advises against travel to a destination as a result of COVID-19.
Always Cheaper than the Gate
Pre-book your tickets for huge savings versus the gate.
Our price promise ensures that you are getting the best value attraction tickets - AttractionTickets.com will not be beaten on price!
Free delivery
We are pleased to offer a FREE 7 day delivery service to all our UK & Ireland customers. No matter how large or small your order is, you will receive free shipping.
Real theme park tickets not vouchers
Receive actual theme park tickets, NOT vouchers and gain access straight into the parks - no fuss!
£25 Deposit
Guarantee our current prices and spread the cost of your Orlando tickets, with a deposit of just £25pp. Balance due 6 weeks prior to your departure.
Destinations
Melbourne
Krakow
Venice
Milan
Florence
Amsterdam
Franz Josef
Over 4 Million Customers ...and
counting!
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The AttractionTickets.com Limited Privacy Policy sets out what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we do with it.
The AttractionTickets.com Limited Privacy Policy sets out what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we do with it.
Using your personal Information
We at ATD Travel Services Ltd understand and respect the importance of your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your personal information. In providing our service to you, we must collect personal information from you and make subsequent use of it as detailed below.
We will only collect, process use, share and store your personal information where we are satisfied that we have an appropriate legal basis to do this. In most cases this is because we need to arrange for you to enter into a contract with suppliers for tickets or other services; but it could also be where you have given us your specific consent to the use of your information, to comply with a relevant legal or regulatory obligation that we have, or for our legitimate interests as a commercial organisation. The policy below sets out the legal basis for our use of your personal information in each relevant situation. You can contact us by emailing  customerservices@attractiontickets.com should you have any questions regarding what you read.
You are responsible for ensuring that other members of your party are aware of the content of our Privacy Policy and consent to your acting on their behalf in all your dealings with us. If you do not agree to our use of your information, we cannot do business with you or accept your booking.
HOW?
We will only collect personal information from you by specifically asking for it:
When you buy a ticket from us over the telephone or via our internet booking facilities.
When you register with us for newsletters, email updates, enter competitions or take part in surveys and customer feedback.
When you write, fax, telephone or email us to make an enquiry.
WHAT INFORMATION WILL WE COLLECT?
We may collect all or some of the following information relating to you or other members of your travelling party:
names and contact details
credit/ debit card or other payment details (these are encrypted on entry for your security)
special requirements such as those relating to any disability or medical condition which may affect the chosen purchase
dietary restrictions (which may disclose your religious beliefs)
travel preferences
Some of the information we collect (such as about health or religion) will only be collected on the condition that we have your positive consent to its use. We will seek this consent when necessary. We will update your information whenever we get the opportunity to keep it current, accurate and complete. If you fail to provide us with this information, we may not be able to plan or confirm your booking.
COOKIES
If our contact and dealing with you is via our website(s), we may use "cookies". A cookie is a small piece of data sent from our web server to your computer and stored in a text file on your hard drive. Cookies allow us to identify your computer but not you personally. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies. We use cookies to measure site usage and related information. If you are making a purchase, we may also use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one web page to another.
WHAT WILL WE DO WITH IT?
For the purpose of providing you with our services, we may disclose the information to the providers of the services making up your contracted arrangements (who could be located outside the UK/EEA). Only information necessary for this purpose will be disclosed.
It may be mandatory (as requested government authorities) when you buy services to take place overseas to disclose your information for immigration, security and anti-terrorism purposes, or any other purposes which they determine appropriate. Even if not mandatory, we may exercise our discretion to assist where appropriate.
We may need to disclose our customer list including any personal information relating to you to a third party who acquires or attempts to acquire all or substantially all of the asset/ stock in our company or our website.
(We may also disclose information to organisations who act as “data processors” on our behalf, or to other organisations who perform business functions on our behalf, some of whom are outside the UK/EEA. These functions include administration, providing services (and contacting you where necessary), customer care, business management and operation, re-organisation/structuring/sale of our business (or our group companies), risk assessment, security and crime prevention/detection, research and analysis, marketing, monitoring, measuring and assessing customer purchasing preferences and trends, dispute resolution, credit checking and debt collection.
We may from time to time contact you with information about special offers, brochures, new products, forthcoming events or competitions. You will be given the opportunity on every communication we send you to indicate that you do not wish to receive our promotional material. Alternatively, if do not wish to receive such information, you may ask us in writing not to receive it.
You may indicate your preference to/not to receive direct marketing material in the relevant opt-in/out boxes or be asked the same by our staff at the time you first supplied us your information (or at the earliest opportunity).
We collect information relating to customer trends and patterns. This information is often used in its aggregate form. We, including our other brands, may disclose aggregate statistics about enquiries made, visitors, customers and sales in order to describe our services to prospective partners, purchasers, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes. No personally identifying information is disclosed.
OUR SECURITY POLICY AND RETENTION OF INFORMATION
We have taken all reasonable steps to have appropriate security measures in place to protect your information. Outside the European Economic Area, controls on data protection may not be as wide as the legal requirements in this country. The transmission of information via the internet is never completely secure. We exclude our liability for personal data lost in transmission to the website.
All sensitive information, including your personal details and credit card information, is kept confidential through the use of a secure socket layer (SSL). This means that information can only be exchanged between you and ATD Travel Services Ltd, and that no third party can access this data. The padlock symbol on your browser shows which pages are covered by this security system.
We will retain information only for as long as it is needed for its original purpose or to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and/or enforce our agreements. Any information no longer required will be deleted or disposed of confidentially and completely. We also have appropriate contractual obligations with our ‘data processors’ to ensure that they comply with the requirements of UK law. However, outside the European Economic Area, controls on data protection may not be as wide as the legal requirements in this country.
WHAT CAN I DO?
If you do not agree to our use of the information as set out above, you should inform us as soon as possible by writing to us at:- ATD Travel Services, 171E Wingate Square, London, SW4 0AN Or by emailing customerservices@attractiontickets.com but please note the implications if you withdraw your consent to us using your information as described. In the first instance, please talk to us directly so we can resolve any problem or query. You also have the right to contact the Information Commissions Office (ICO) if you have any questions about Data Protection. You can contact them using their help line 0303 123 113 or at www.ico.org.uk. You may ask us in writing for a copy of the information we hold about you (for which we may charge a fee if your request is excessive) and to correct any inaccuracies in your information and in some circumstances to delete or block the information we hold about you; to complete and restrict its use, and to port it to another organisation. You have the right to request additional information about the handling of your personal data and to object to the processing of your data in some circumstances. Where we have asked for consent to process your data, you may withdraw this consent. Please note that we may not be able to provide some of these services if your request requires disproportionate effort on our part and any information that we do hold may already have been destroyed in line with our data retention policy (see above). We aim to respond to you within 21 days from the date of request. You have the right to ask in writing not to receive direct marketing material about our products.
MONITORING
To ensure that we carry out your instructions accurately, to help improve our service and in the interest of security, we may monitor and/or record: (1) your telephone calls; and (2) customer transactions and activities on our website. All recordings are and shall remain our sole property.
UPDATES AND CHANGES
Any changes to this Policy will be either posted on our website, made available on request or supplied with your next booking with us. We will strive to ensure our practices comply with the most current available version of this Policy.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website(s) may contain links to other sites not controlled by us. (1) These sites may send you cookies and collect data and personal information. We are not responsible for the actions, content or the privacy policies of those websites to which our website(s) may link. It is your responsibility to check the status of these sites.
Our commitment to GDPR
What is GDPR?
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is a regulation by which the European Parliament, the Council of the European Union and the European Commission intend to reinforce data protection for everyone within the European Union. It defines new laws based on a set of principles that businesses which handle personal data of EU citizens must follow.
The major principles of GDPR require that personal data should be:
Processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner in relation to individuals.
Collected for specified, explicit and legitimate purposes and not further processed in a manner that is incompatible with those purposes; further processing for archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes shall not be considered to be incompatible with the initial purposes.
Adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary in relation to the purposes for which they are processed.
4. Accurate and, where necessary, kept up to date; every reasonable step must be taken to ensure that personal data that are inaccurate, having regard to the purposes for which they are processed, are erased or rectified without delay.
Kept in a form which permits identification of data subjects for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data are processed; personal data may be stored for longer periods insofar as the personal data will be processed solely for archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes subject to implementation of the appropriate technical and organisational measures required by the GDPR in order to safeguard the rights and freedoms of individuals.
Processed in a manner that ensures appropriate security of the personal data, including protection against unauthorised or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage, using appropriate technical or organisational measures.
What are we actually doing?
We take data security and privacy of our customers extremely seriously. We are constantly reviewing our systems and processes to ensure we abide by the GDPR principles. This is not limited to, but involves new policies and procedures for the following:
Internal access and permissions to view/edit data
Encryption of data in rest, transit and backup
Customer consent
Data minimisation and quality
Customer requests for rectification, portability or deletion
Network security
Breech notification
SSL
All sensitive information, including your personal details and credit card information, is kept confidential through the use of a secure socket layer (SSL). This means that information can only be exchanged between you and AttractionTickets.com, and that no third party can access this data. The padlock symbol on your browser shows which pages are covered by this security system. Please refer to our privacy policy for more information.
We hope that you won’t ever need to, but if you do want to complain about our use of personal data, please send an email with the details of your complaint to customerservices@attractiontickets.com. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the UK data protection regulator, the Information Commissioner's Office (“ICO”). For further information on your rights and how to complain to the ICO, please refer to the ICO website https://ico.org.uk/concerns
close
Your Basket
It's in the bag!
Added
View basket
Checkout
